- Dre, you're ready?
- Yeah, one second.
Oh Dre, I am so excited!
It's like we are brave pioneers,
on a quest to start a new life
in a magical, new land.
You could say that.
Okay, all right, let's go.
- And don't forget to use the bathroom.
- Okay.
Be careful with that guys, okay?
- I'll see you later, uncle Charlie.
- C'mon Dre, we can't miss this plane!
Bye guys!
We're gonna miss you.
- No man, it's yours.
- C'mon Dre, just take it.
Thanks, man!
Okay Dre, c'mon, we have to go.
Okay, bye guys!
We'll call you as soon as we land.
- Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to flight CA982.
- You got it? - Yeah.
- With our service to Beijing.
- Oh Dre look, we are already on lesson ten.
How are you?
- Remember what that one is?
- No.
Dre, you're killing me.
Mom, look, in China everything is old.
There's old houses, old parks...
old people...Look, this guy is at least
four-hundred years old.
Dre, please focus.
Okay?
What's your name?
You need to practice.
Yeah, you need to try.
No, mom.
- Yes, Dre. Dre...
- Mom?
- Ask him. Go ahead.
- No, mom.
Ask him "what's your name"
and "how are you". Do it, now.
Dude, I'm from Detroit.
What's up?
It's said to meet her
at number five.
Mrs. Packer?
- Hi. It's Parker.
- Oh, apologies, Mrs. Parker. Welcome to Beijing.
Look! There is Omatek village.
Isn't it beautiful?
Yes. I guess there's nothing
old in China, huh Dre?
Look at that, Dre. Beverly Hills.
We've always talked about
living there, huh?
I think we have talked
about the other one, mom.
I got a good feeling about this.
Oh, yeah. You must be the new
dude in 305. I'm Harry.
- Hey, what's up? I'm Dre.
- Here. Let me help you.
Thanks, man.
- Welcome to the building, Dre.
- Thanks.
Can you please explain this electricity card,
because we-we don't have these in America.
- Know any Chinese?
- Nah.
This is China.
Might not be a bad idea.
Oh, that's our park.
You should come.
Look at you.
Making friends already.
- Hi, I'm Dre's mother.
- Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you too.
You can call me Miss Sherry.
- I'm Harry.
- Hi, Harry.
- So, I guess, I'll see you later, then?
- Maybe.
Okay, cool. See you.
Ok, this is your rental agreement in English.
So the landlady is Mrs. Wong.
Her English is not good.
But if something goes wrong,
you go to Mr. Han.
- His English is very good.
- Okay.
Okay. So, welcome to Beijing, Mrs. Parker.
Um, so I see you tomorrow, okay?
Okay, sure! Thank you.
Oh, wait, wait!
Um, you mentioned something
about going...
Oh, this is perfect, Dre. Everything we
need is in walking distance.
Oh, you know what,
we can have lunch together
every day at your school,
if you wanted to.
Negative! Not a chance.
Dre, we are not doing this in Beijing.
Dre, pick up your jacket!
Mom, I'm tired, okay?
I have airplane lag.
Airplane...
It's jet lag.
I know baby, I got it too.
But, we can't go to sleep. Cause then we'll
be up at 2 A.M. You have school tomorrow.
Dre, can you please go
find the maintenance man?!
I need to take a shower,
and the hot water is broken!
Yes.
Excuse me.
Um, the maintenance man?
Mr. Han?
Thanks.
Me and my mom, we just moved in. 305.
The hot water is not working.
Mr. Han?
Okay. Alright I just come back another time.
Or you can just show me how to do it so,
I can get out of your hair.
Um, I can always come back
if this is bad time.
- Hey man, you made it. Welcome.
- Thanks.
- You play, right? C'mon.
- Yeah.
- Us three against them four.
- All right.
Pass!
What's up?
My shooting hand.
Got some jet lag so...
You know, I'm just...
You want this?
You want me to play? You know
I have no problem beatin' old people.
Back where I come from they call me
"Ping Pong Dre", alright?
I'm going to take it easy on you.
Come on, man.
I'm twelve.
He is really good.
I've never seen him lose to anybody.
Yeah.
- Dude. You're gonna talk to her or what?
- To who?
- To her. The girl you've been staring at.
- I wasn't staring at her, dude.
Yeah, you were.
- You should go talk to her, unless you're scared?
- I'm not scared of anything.
Then do it. Go.
Come on.
Right now.
Hey, what's up?
I forgot.
No English, um...
What language was that?
You speak English?
Me too.
- So, what are you listening to?
- Bach.
Bach, I listen to them all the time.
They are tight. Have you ever heard of this?
Oh yeah, you like it huh, right?!
Great move, one over here.
- Wait, wait it's coming back.
- May I touch your hair?
You want to touch my hair?
Um...Sure.
You shoud be practicing.
I'm practicing.
- What you're doing, you won't be needing these.
- What's your problem?
Leave it.
Come on, dude.
I said, leave it.
You want to fight?
- Are you okay?
- Leave me alone.
I'm fine.
- Dre, dude...
- Leave me alone.
Dre, are you ready?
Cause we got to be there in like 20 minutes.
I know, mom.
- And you have your uniform on, right?
- Yes, mom.
Don't break any rules
on the first day.
Okay, come on, I'm waiting for you.
Wait, you don't have to comin', I mean...
I can handle it.
Dre, don't be silly, it's your first day.
Plus, we both have to meet the
assist principal Mrs. Pong.
I can find her.
You need to get to work, right?!
- Are you trying to get rid of me?
- No, mom.
Mrs. Pong.
Hi, Mrs. Pong.
- Mrs. Parker,  we've been waiting.
- I'm so sorry we are late...
We just flew from Detroit last night...
- And this is my son Dre.
- Hello.
- We only wear uniforms on Uniform day.
- Oh, that's my fault.
I didn't have a chance to read the school packages
sent to me. Will be better tomorrow.
- And hats are not permitted.
- Yeah, I should've read up on the dress code.
- Dre, is that make-up? What is that?
- Mom, I ran into a pole.
- No, you have a black eye. You've got into a fight?
- Fighting is not tolerated here.
You heard him, he ran into a pole.
Come here, Dre.
- Mom, don't start.
- Who did it?
Nobody mom, I ran into a pole. I ain't tell
you cause I know you would react like this.
Dre, you know I don't play,
if somebody hit my baby, I would tear...
I know mom,
that's why I don't tell you stuff.
- Just relax, I just ran into a...
- Yeah, yeah,  you ran into a pole.
Alright Dre, alright, alright. Look, go to class,
go to  class, but we will talk about this later.
Okay? Alright, go!
- I love you.
- Mom?!
I said I love you.
- Okay, I love you too.
- Okay, have a good day.
- Hi.
- Hey!
You know,
we only wear uniforms on Uniform day.
Oh yeah, I still got that one.
Thanks.
- I'm Meiying.
- I'm Dre.
Sorry about Cheng.
So that's his name?!
- Is he your boyfriend?
- No.
- Our parents are very close.
- He definitely likes you.
- I have to go practice.
- Wait...
- You eat and practice at the same time?
- Yes.
But, my mom says if you eat standing up,
it gives you gas.
You're funny.
- Come to fix the hot water.
- It's in there.
Kid?
Kid?!
Did you just hit me in my neck
with a toothpaste cap?!
Hot water fine.
Flip switch.
Wait half hour, take shower,
flip switch off.
Why don't you just leave it on?
- You leave on in America?
- We don't have a switch in America.
Get switch,
Save planet.
- What happened to your eye?
- I ran into a pole.
Interesting pole.
- Dre?! I'm back.
- That's my mom.
End it, do the handle, it's messed up.
- Are you ready for school?
- Yeah.
- Hey, let me help you.
- They have your favorite cereal here, I found it.
Dre, for the one hundredth time,
can you please pick up your jacket?
- One second, mom.
- No! Not in one second, now!
This programme is about to be over.
Give me two minutes.
Dre, I don't care!
Come and pick it up now.
- God, how many times do I have to ask you?
- Once.
- That's right. Make it happen.
- "What's with you and the jacket?!"
- I'm sorry, what was that?
- Nothing.
Okay, just what I thought...
Nothing.
Thank you.
From the top again.
Okay. It's enough please. You are rushing it.
You must play the pauses.
Do you know how important this is for your family?
What it will mean for your life?
We have to work this weekend.
I'm calling you father.
We continue.
- How that sound?
- Almost like a Chinese.
Yeah, I'm fluent. And I don't know about that guy
was talking about? I thought you sounded great.
Thank you.
- So, you are practicing for anything? Like a show?
- Yes, I have an audition next month...
- For the Beijing Academy of Music.
- Beijing Academy of Music. Sounds important.
You know, their initials spell BAM.
What?
I gotta go.
Can I touch your hair?
You're gonna do something?
Just stay away from us.
All of us.
Baby?!
Dre, are you sleeping?
- Um, can you sign this?
- For the Forbidden City?!
I think it's funny that you have to give
my permission to go to the Forbidden City.
- Pole in Beijing.
- Not funny, mom.
Oh, cut it out, grumpy.
I'm serious, Dre. This ice cream,
I don't know what they do it,
but it's more flavoristic. What?
Mom, this is you. "Oh my Godness, this ice cream
here is so good, and everything in China...
is so much better than everything else..."
Aw, mom c'mon...
First of all, I don't sound like that,
and I don't move all like that.
You should get some ice cream, sweetie.
- Mom, mom,  c'mon.
- Dre! Wait!
Boy, you won't get running from me?!
Kung Fu.
What do we learn here?
No weakness! No pain! No mercy!
Begin!
- Mom, mom, c'mon, let's go. C'mon, mom!
- What? Dre, we just got here.
- Dre, what's going on?
- Nothing.
- Dre, what happened?
- Nothing happened.
What is it, you don't want to take that class?
Whatever Dre, What happened?
We moved to China!
That's what happened!
Okay, stop.
Don't be like that, Dre.
What do you want me to do?
- We've been here less than a week...
- I feel like it's a year!
I hate it here.
Dre, please let me help you.
I can't help you if you don't tell
me what's wrong?! Oh, please.
You don't care what's wrong!
All you care about is how happy I am
and how great ice cream is.
I'm not happy.
I hate it here!
I want to go home!
Dre, we can't go home. Okay?
There is nothing left for us in Detroit.
This is what we've got.
This is home.
Gather on here.
Welcome to one of the most popular
landmarks in all over China.
It is visited by millions of people
every year.
The Forbidden City.
You plaster on for good luck.
- I wish someone would just...
- Yeah, me too.
- Just tell someone.
- Yeah, I got it.
Thanks a lot.
The walls of the palace were reinforced
with the bricks, 15 layers deep,
to prevent anyone
from coming in.
- Mr. Parker... Is everything okay?
- Oh yes?
Um...Yes, thank you.
Get him.
Come on.
You're fast.
But not fast enough.
He's had enough.
Don't you remember what we learned?
No weakness. No pain.
No mercy!
Go home.
- What's up with the light bulbs, Mr. Han?
- Shh!
I thought you are just a maintenance man?
You've seen only with your eyes,
so you are easy to fool.
It doesn't hurt.
Chauva.
Ancient Chinese healing.
How did you do that up there? You like even
didn't punch them. They...beat each other up.
When fighting angry, blind men...
best we just stay out of the way.
- So, where did you learn Kung Fu?
- From father.
Have you ever taught anybody?
No.
Would you?
- Depends.
- On what?
- Reason.
- What about to kick somebody's ass?
The best fights are the ones we avoid.
What if I wanna avoid getting
my ass kicked?
- Stop saying "ass".
- Sorry.
Kung Fu is for knowledge, defense.
Not to make war,
but to create peace.
That's not definitely what they're taught.
No such thing as bad student,
only bad teacher.
That's great. I guess we'll just stroll in
their school and talk to their teacher.
- Good idea.
- No, bad idea.
If I go in there, I get my ass kick...
- I'll get beat up.
- You got beat up anyway.
Would you go with me?
No, sorry.
- But you said it was a good idea.
- For you, bad idea for me.
C'mon, it's not like you should be busy
or anything...I don't even speak Chinese.
Very sorry.
Okay...Whatever.
Wait!
What are you doing?
Why did you stop?
Finish!
Okay, Mr. Han, let's get out of here.
We do not stop when our enemy is down!
No mercy.
No mercy in the studio.
No mercy in life.
What are you looking at?
He's the one that attacked me.
We are here to make peace.
Let your little thing mind himself.
One to one, no problem...Six to one,
too much to ask of anyone.
I see.
Prepare for match!
Whoa Mr. Han, does he want us to fight?
We are not here to fight.
You attack my students
and disrespect my studio?!
You want to leave?
Not so easy.
Master Li...
You both came here.
One of you fights now.
The boy will fight there.
OPEN KUNG FU TOURNAMENT
We accept your challenge.
Please instruct your students
to leave my boy alone to train.
Attention!
From now on the little thing
is to be left alone...
until the tournament.
- Understood?!
- Yes!
If he does not show up
for the competition...
I will bring pain to him and you.
So, that go pretty much
how you planned it?
There's good news and bad news.
The good news is they promised
to leave you alone.
- Really?
- While you prepare.
Prepare for what?
The tournament.
You'll fight them all, one by one.
Huh?
So the bad news is now
they get to beat me up in public.
- Yes.
- Great. Thanks. Thanks a lot.
They're gonna kill me.
You saw their Kung Fu.
That's not Kung Fu. That does not
represent China.
That bad man teach them really bad
things that hurt, a lot.
More good news.
I will teach you real Kung Fu.
Yes.
- See you later, mom.
- Hey, wait. This is early for you for a Saturday.
- Mr. Han will teach me Kung Fu.
- The maintenance man?
It's China mom,
everybody knows Kung Fu.
Dre, you know how do I feel about
your fighting.
Kung Fu is not fight mom, it's about
making peace with your enemy.
- Be careful, Dre.
- Yeah.
Mr. Han?
- Mr. Han?
- Back here.
You know you have a car
in your living room, Mr. Han?
Okay, I was thinking about yesterday. I know
I was kinda freaking out about the tournament...
but I realized something last night.
I'm an athlete. My number one asset
is I'm fast, okay?!
I'm quick. I'm quick.
Got the speed. Cat speed.
You see? I'm quick yeah, you see?
In the US, I used to take gymnastic at PAL,
that's Police Athletic League, to check it,
right?
Boom. You see that?
My Uncle Reymi used to date that
Brazilian girl and he learned Jiu-Jitsu.
And he taught some of it to me.
As like, locks and holds and stuff, it's okay.
Attack me.
You see that? Feel that?
I can break it.
I'm choosing not to.
To press your luck. It's dangerous.
And he also taught me Capoeira so...
Can't touch me. Can't touch...
Was that antique?
Pick up your jacket.
So basically Mr. Han,
what I'm trying to say is...
I got a good foundation here.
You know, like I said. I'm just...
Might not be as hard to teach me
as other people, you know.
- Hang it up.
- Okay.
- Happy now?
- Take it down.
- You just...
Put it on.
Take it off.
- I already did all of this.
- Take it off.
Can you just tell me,
why I'm doing this?
Take it off.
Hang it up.
Take it down.
Put it on the ground.
Pick it up.
Hang up.
Take it down.
Put it on.
Take it off.
Put it on the ground.
Pick it up.
Hang it up.
Take it down.
Put it on.
Take it off.
Hang it up.
Mr. Han, why do you have
a car in your living room?
No street parking.
Hey!
So how did it go?
What you learned?
Nothing.
Uniform on Uniform day.
- You're fighting in the tournament?
- Yeah, how did you hear?
Everybody knows.
- I hope you have a good teacher.
- Yeah, me too.
He's a maintenance man.
- Can I ask you a question?
- Yes.
Well, I know you're practicing, and I think I'm practicing, I mean,
I don't know what I'm doing...
- But, we both kind of practicing, you know and...
- Are you going to that Shi-Shi festival?
Yeah, I mean, I've missed
the Shi-Di Festival since I've been in China.
- Go to the Shaolin theater.
- Okay. You want me to meet you?
Oh, oh, so like Shaolin theater, okay Shi-Fi-Shi festival.
Shaolin theater, okay. Cool.
- When is it again?
- Tomorrow. The show starts at seven.
Okay. So tomorrow, Shaolin theater.
Shi-Shi festival at seven.
- See you tomorrow.
- Shi-Shi festival.
- Festival. - Shi-Shi festival.
- Okay. - Okay.
Mr. Han?
- Mr. Han, can I come in?
- You may come in.
Where's your jacket?
- I thought, I was warmin' up without it.
- Go get it.
You want me to go
all way back, just to get it?
Yes, all the way back
where you hide it.
- This is not right.
- What? I'm doing it.
No.
- Something is missing.
- Nothing is missing.
You forgot, this.
Attitude.
Shake it off.
Yes, that's it.
Okay, Mr. Han. I get it. I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have treated my mom like that.
You're right.
- Put it on the ground.
- Hello.
Ow, hey mom.
Um, did you get the tickets?
Yes, I got the tickets,
and I got an extra one for Mr. Han.
- But I didn't say...
- Dre, stop it.
Mr. Han, would you like to go with us
to the Shi-Shi festival?
No, thank you.
Too many people.
- Yeah, mom. Way too many people.
- Yeah, but I already bought the tickets.
- I don't go...
- Mr. Han, I'm not taking "no" for an answer.
You'll have fun. You need
to get out the house, okay?
Here are your clothes, Dre.
Come on, hurry up and change.
Dre...
Pick up your jacket!
You were right Mr. Han,
there are a lot of people here.
Chinese Valentine's Day.
Yeah, Mom. I'm going to go get something
to eat, then going to go to the bathroom.
Be back, right here,
in 20 minutes.
- I love you.
- I love you, too. Be careful. 20 minutes.
- 20.
- Okay.
I got this, and this for you.
I downloaded this.
It has a very cool violins stuff, and I...
I thought maybe you could play along and...
It's not like Bach and...
but, I thought maybe
you'd like it and...
- So, um, do you have any kids?
- No.
Oh, how's Dre doing?
- Um, Shao Dre making a progress.
- Shao Dre?
Yes, Chinese pollito.
So, um, how many students do you have?
- Including Shao Dre?
- Yeah.
One.
So, what's the show about?
It's the story of the Goddess...
and a boy she loves.
I love this story.
Her mother does not approve of him.
So, she cuts a wide river in the sky
to separate them forever.
But once a year,
all the birds in the sky...
felt sad for them,
and they form a bridge.
So the two of them may be
together for a single night.
I'll be there at you audition,
if you come to my tournament.
- Okay, I'll be there.
- Pinky swear.
See, you wrap your hands like this.
I swear that I'll be there at your audition,
no matter what happens.
And I promise to cheer bigger
than anyone else when you win.
What up, Mr. Han?
Did I say come in?
Um, I think you did. I mean...
- Mr. Han, can I please come in?
- Yes.
- So, what we are doing today?
- Same.
Mr. Han, I told you. I get it, okay?
Be respectful! I got it!
I put my jacket on a thousand times,
and I took it off a thousand times, okay?
This is stupid. I'm done!
Let them beat me up,
if they want to.
You know why you only have
one student? 'Cause you don't know Kung Fu.
- Shao Dre!
- What?
Come here.
- Jacket on!
- Mr. Han, I already...- Jacket on!
- I don't have a jacket...- Jacket on!
Be strong.
Jacket on.
Firm.
Jacket off.
Remember...
always strong...
Jacket off.
Strong.
Left foot back.
Right foot back.
Pick up your jacket!
- Whoa, Mr. ...- Focus!
- Okay. - Always concentrate.
Left back. Right foot back.
Pick up your jacket!
Stay.
Pick up your jacket.
Strong.
Hang it up.
And attitude!
Strike!
Hang up and attitude!
Harder.
Good, but no face.
Jacket off!
Kung Fu lives in everything
we do, Shao Dre.
It lives in how we put on a jacket,
and how we take off the jacket.
It lives in
how we treat people.
Everything is Kung Fu.
- So, why do not we take the Shiroko?
- I don't drive the Shiroko.
- Do you have a license?
- Yes.
So you have a license and a car
and we're in the train?
- Please, be quiet.
- I'm just sayin'...
seems like we could've saved
a lot of money, don't you think?
- Do you always ask these many questions?
- I'm sorry.
So, what we are learning today?
Chi.
Eternal Energy.
The essence of life.
It moves inside of us,
flows through our bodies.
Give us power from within.
I get it,
like the "Force" from Star Wars.
You're Yoda,
and I'm like... I'm like a Jedi.
- Is this where you learned Kung Fu?
- Yes.
Everything good about me
was born here.
So Dre, you gotta leave your backpack
and skateboard here.
- So, where are we going?
- The journey to the top of the mountain.
Tomb of the Dragon Well.
Dragon Well? It's probably,
closer than it is, I'm looking at it.
Right?
- Are we there yet?
- Soon.
- How do you say water in Chinese?
- Shui.
I need some shui.
I'm really thirsty.
- I'm thirsty, Mr. Han.
- Water on top of the mountain.
Shao Dre.
The journey is complete.
- This is the Dragon Well?
- Yes.
I stood here with my father,
when I was your age.
He told me that's the magic
Kung Fu water.
You drink and nothing
can defeat you.
It's the best water I've ever tasted.
- Did you see the lady with the snake?
- Yes.
She was doing the Cobra thing.
She was like...
copying the snake. And it was like...
right here, and she was like...
You did not watch closely enough,
Shao Dre.
The snake was copying the woman.
What? I don't get it.
Look.
- What do you see?
- Me, well my reflection. - Yes.
- Now, what do you see?
- It's blurry. - Yes.
That woman was sliced through water
quiet and calm.
In here and in here.
So, the snake reflects her action,
like still water.
- Like a mirror?
- Yes.
So, she controlled a snake
by doing nothing?
Being still and doing nothing,
are two very different things.
- She used her Chi on that snake, didn't she?
- Very good.
You gotta teach me that.
How to control people.
There is only one person
you need to learn how to control.
Who?
Empty your mind.
Flow with my movement.
Connect to the energy,
around you.
- I kinda just want to learn the cobra thing.
- Cobra takes a lifetime.
- Requires great focus.
- But I have great focus?!
- Oh my God. Mr. Han...
- Your focus,
- needs more focus.
- Mr. Han...
Thank you, Mr. Han.
There's no such thing
as fortune cookies in China.
Dre, please be careful
crossing the street.
You just scared the life out of me,
the other day. They have the "right-of-way".
And the symbols. I can't get
the symbols right on the bathrooms.
And I'm still walkin' into the men's restroom.
The other day I walked in,
there was this 90 years old Chinese man,
he thought he was getting a little treat.
Dre, please stop that! You look crazy!
Here, eat your noodles!
Mr. Han,
what's goin' on?
Anticipation.
I can't see...
Don't see it, feel it.
Dammit, Mr. Han!
I felt that one!
- Mr. Han.
- What?
- Concentrate, okay?
- Okay. Do I get the stick now?
- Dre, you okay?
- I'm okay.
What's up Mr. Han, what time
we are trainin' tomorrow?
Shao Dre, we are not training tomorrow.
Why not?
- Wu chi pi fan
- Wu chi pi fan?
It means: "Too much of something
is not good."
You train a lot, you need to rest.
A day off?
Yes, Mr. Han! Yes!
Shao Dre needs to rest.
Yes, Mr. Han.
You rest, too.
I love you, Mr. Han. Peace!
Are you okay?
- My audition is tomorrow at a six.
- Isn't it what you've been practicing for?
- Yes, of course.
- Don't worry, you got it.
What if they don't pick me?
Meiying, wait!
First of all,
I'm going to be there with you.
And B, all you have to do is what your
teacher says. Play the pauses.
It's easy, watch.
You see?
- I have to practice.
- Wait.
Wu gi bi fan.
What?
I'm sorry,
I don't think you don't speak Chinese.
Wu gi bi fan.
Too much of good stuff is a bad stuff?
Ow...Wu chi pi fan.
Yeah.
Wu gi bi FUN.
- Come on.
- Where are we going?
Have you ever been to the gym?
C'mon, we are going to have some fun.
Come on, I know you want
to go have some fun!
Okay, that's going to give you
some serious gas.
- What do you see?
- Me.
- Now, what do you see?
Go, come on.
You're dancing machine.
That was pretty good!
Here comes, round two.
You're hot.
-That's like American dancing.
Like, you should have a group. -No.
With like, other people in it
dancing behind you, doin' the same stuff.
- The audition, it was changed to today.
- But they said, it's tomorrow.
Something happened.
It is in 20 minutes.
My father is coming to get me.
Hey, she's like totally going to get it, right,
because that was just great.
Hey! That was fantastic.
That was... You just...
You played so beautifully, and...
We can no longer be friends.
You are bad for my life.
See you at the tournament.
Don't be late for that.
Mr. Han!
We'll not train today.
- What are you doing?
- It's July 8th.
Why did you wreck the car?
His name was Kang Kang.
Shao Dre, how old are you?
Twelve.
He was ten.
He was so beautiful.
Her name was Xiang.
She was a singer.
Not professional.
She sang only for me.
What happened?
There was a steep hill.
Lots of rain.
The car, it just...
I was driving.
We argued about something.
I was so angry.
I lost control.
I try to remember...
but I can not remember what we're
argued about.
I hope it was something important.
Every year, I fix the car.
But still fix nothing.
Mr. Han!
Win or lose, doesn't matter.
Fight hard.
Earn respect.
The boys leave you alone.
I have a present for you.
Oh! Mr. Han.
This is the one Bruce Lee had.
Great.
Thank you.
You have taught me
a very important lesson, Shao Dre.
Life will knock us down, but we can
choose, whether or not,  to get back up.
You're the best friend
I've ever had, Mr. Han.
Okay.
Wait!
Can you help me with something?
Dre?
Is your dad home?
Sir...
My name is Dre Parker.
My actions have brought
dishonor to your family.
Your daughter has been
a great friend to me.
And from her I have learned...
...that a true friend...
...is a person
who makes your life better.
But, if you give me a second chance...
...I promise that I will be...
...the best friend your
daughter has ever had.
That's it.
My daughter told me that she made
a promise to be at your tournament.
In our family,
we do not break our promises.
Good luck!
Thank you.
Rock and roll.
Let the tournament begin!
Shao Dre, you're up.
- What's that?
- The rule book.
- You don't know the rules?
- Of course I know the rules, it's simple.
You hit him,
and don't let him hit you.
What?
Mr. Han, they're going to kill me.
Two points to win. Win it two times.
Go. Focus. Focus.
That's a warning.
You cannot run off the mat.
Next time you lose a point.
Go.
- Be strong.
- Come on, Dre.
- Good job. Next time, no face.
- I'm sorry, I can't help it.
The next point winner.
Come on, baby.
Dre Parker advances to the semi-finals!
From now on, the semi-final matches,
three points to win.
Be kinda hot if I
won this thing, huh, Mr. Han?
- Be kinda hot if you focused.
- Yeah, well, after that.
And now the 1st semi-final
of the evening.
TOURNAMENT OF CHAMPIONS
SEMI-FINAL
First round:
Cheng Vs. Wu Ping.
Cheng advances to final.
Next semi-final:
Introducing Fighting Dragon Liang...
...and the surprising finalist, Dre Parker.
Empty your mind. Focus.
You're disqualified!
Are you okay?
He's done.
I'm sorry, you should not continue.
You've brought honor to your family.
The doctor says, you did great.
- You okay, baby?
- Yeah, I'm okay.
Dre Parker has 2 minutes to
return to the match.
If he's unable to return...
...the Fighting Dragons
win by default.
Can you guys give us a second?
Yeah, okay. Sure baby,
whatever you need.
Do you think I could have won?
Win or lose doesn't matter,
Shao Dre.
You know that's not what I mean.
Yes, I think you had a good chance.
So, let's do the fiery cup thing.
You don't need to fight anymore.
You have proven everything you need to prove.
What, that I can get
beat up easy, and then quit?
That's not balance,
that's not real Kung Fu.
You said, when life knocks you down,
you could choose whether or not to get back up.
Well, I'm tryin' to get back up.
And why won't you help me?
Because...
I cannot watch you
get hurt anymore.
Please, Mr. Han. Please.
Just tell me, Shao Dre. Why?
Why you need to go back out there so badly?
Because I'm still scared.
No matter what happens tonight
when I leave...
...I don't want to be scared anymore.
Since Dre Parker has
not returned to the ring...
Dre Parker will fight!
Shao Dre?
Come on, Dre.
You can do this, Dre.
- You okay?
- Yes, I'm okay.
No mercy.
The score is tied.
The next point wins!
I'm so proud of you.
Transcript by: (radojka & Don4EveR)
www.subscene.com